{
    "easy": [
        {
            "question": "How do you get a music disc",
            "choices": [
                "In loot chests at y=-1 in the void",
                "When a creeper is killed by a skeleton",
                "When a skeleton is killed by a creeper",
                "When a zombie is summoned by a griefer"            
            ],
            "answer": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "How do you break obsidian",
            "choices": [
                "With a wooden pick -- its easy",
                "With a lot of creepers",
                "With tnt",
                "with a diamond/netherite pick"            
            ],
            "answer": 3
        },
        {
            "question": "How do you get a grass block",
            "choices": [
                "You just mine it",
                "With a tool enchanted with silk touch",
                "With tnt",
                "With a enderite pick"            
            ],
            "answer": 1
        }
    ],
    "medium": [
        {
            "question": "Which nametags alter a vex",
            "choices": [
                "Dinnerbone/Grumm",
                "Dinnerbone/jeb_",
                "Grumm/Johnny",
                "Johnny/Toast"
            ],
            "answer": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "What enchantment kills skeletons faster",
            "choices": [
                "Speed Kill",
                "You can't",
                "Sweeping Edge",
                "Smite"
            ],
            "answer": 3
        },
        {
            "question": "You can get efficiency 5 on an enchanting table. True or False",
            "choices": [
                "True",
                "False"
            ],
            "answer": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "How do you get lime dye without crafting",
            "choices": [
                "Cactus",
                "You can't",
                "Sea Pickles",
                "By shearing a zombie"
            ],
            "answer": 2
        }
    ],
    "hard": [       
        {
            "question": "When do tamed parrots not dance to discs",
            "choices": [
                "Just play a disc",
                "Play 13",
                "When you untame it",
                "When you tame it while the music is playing"
            ],
            "answer": 3
        },

        {
            "question": "What enchantment can turn turtles to bowls",
            "choices": [
                "Abracadabra",
                "None",
                "Channeling",
                "Fire Aspect"
            ],
            "answer": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "Can tridents float",
            "choices": [
                "True",
                "False"
            ],
            "answer": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "What type of bastion have gold trophy-like structures",
            "choices": [
                "Bridge",
                "Stable",
                "Housing",
                "Treasure"
            ],
            "answer": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "What remains common in every Minecraft Java world other than the player",
            "choices": [
                "Mobs",
                "Tree Generation",
                "Bedrock Generation",
                "Nothing"
            ],
            "answer": 2
        }
    ],
    "really": [
        {
            "question": "What changes through updates in a world (even when loaded)",
            "choices": [
                "Loot chests",
                "Structures",
                "Villager",
                "Nothing"
            ],
            "answer": 0
        },

        {
            "question": "When does it rain in the nether",
            "choices": [
                "Never",
                "When you go far quickly",
                "When you are in a basalt delta",
                "When water clips into the overworld"
            ],
            "answer": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Which version removed getting wither heads from strays (Bedrock)",
            "choices": [
                "1.14",
                "1.15",
                "1.16",
                "It was never added"
            ],
            "answer": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "Which of these is a splash text",
            "choices": [
                "Philza had a good run!",
                "The bees knees!",
                "Honey, I waxed the copper!",
                "1234 is a bad password!"
            ],
            "answer": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "Which direction does a loyalty trident face when you throw it",
            "choices": [
                "North",
                "South",
                "East",
                "West"
            ],
            "answer": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "If a creeper explodes because of another creeper two blocks away, how many punches kill the creeper",
            "choices": [
                "It's dead",
                "1",
                "2",
                "3"
            ],
            "answer": 1
        }
    ]
}
    
